

## **Contact**

Phone

+374-95-14-49-48

**Email** 

arshak\_kosakyan23@alumni.aua.am

Address

33/2 Aram Khachatryan St, Yerevan, Armenia

## **Skills**

- React.js/Three.js/JavaScript
- HTML5/CSS/SASS
- JAVA
- MySQL
- WordPress
- Web Design

# Languages

Armenian

English

Russian

## **Portfolio**

<u>https://poseidon-web-portfolio.netlify.app/</u>

# **ARSHAK KOSAKYAN**

FRONTEND DEVELOPER/REACT JS 3+ YEARS EXPERIENCE

### **About Me**

A well-disciplined, ambitious, and dedicated professional with experience working in a fast-paced startup environment. Have demonstrated experience for over one year in creating digital designs and self-branding websites. Throughout my career, I have completed various digital marketing products and websites. Have a logical mind with a practical approach to problem-solving and have proven experience working in deadline-driven environments with a drive to see things through to completion. Have served for two years in the Armenian Army forces.

## **Education**

**Sep 2017 - Jun 2023** American University of Armenia **BS in Computer Science** 

Sep 2022 - Feb 2023

TCO Academy

**Front-End Web Developer** 

## **Experience**

#### MyBrokerSearch Jun 2021-Jun2022

Web Developer

- Developed marketing materials for brokers, real estate agents, insurance agents, and loan agents in the USA, including digital cards, flyers, and videos.
- Collaborated with the design team to create high-quality content such as blog posts, landing pages, brochures, proposals, presentations, emails, and newsletters.
- Designed customizable branding websites for clients and implemented necessary modifications.
- Integrated an IDX software into clients' websites, enabling property search and live website functionality.
- Managed website security and functionality, ensuring regular updates.

#### Team2B Apr 2023-Present

Web Developer

- Web development with a focus on WordPress and WooCommerce for Armenian companies.
- Experienced in creating custom themes and plugins for WordPress.
- Skilled in frontend development with React.js.
- Ensure responsive design and optimize websites for performance and usability.
- Provide ongoing maintenance and support for websites.